know that we have inserted the text into
the presentation it's time to think
about the actual for money available at
the moment the presentation contains
four slade's with a plain white
background and some text what I need to
do I want to try and enhance the
document and the first thing I'm going
to do is insert some images on the first
slate so if I select insert and there's
a variety of tools along here but I'm
going to focus on inserting a couple of
pictures so if I select a picture icon
and the first pitch I'm going to insert
is from this device I've already got
that see it on my computer so if I
select that and then take me to the
location well see if the image and then
double click on it or not insert that
into the presentation as you can see
there are a number of icons around the
edge of the image if I click and hold on
was they allow me to resize the image I
can also rotate the image accordingly if
you wish to maintain the aspect ratio
you should ensure that you use the
corner buttons to change the size of the
picture so now I've inserted the first
pitch and would look for another one and
if I click on insert again select
picture and this time I'm going to go
for a stock image so I look for a stock
image and I'm going to do a search for
balloon and that will bring up a range
of images relating to balloon and I will
just select that one that will insert
that into the slate as you can see it's
very large so again I need to resize up
and reduce the size down so I used two
corner table to do that and then place
it there there's a little bit a little
bit bigger again so it's more consistent
with the other image or cube so now I
have the two images in I can apply a
range of formatting to the actual images
so if I click and select an image and
then go to the picture styles and move
my mouse over the various icons and will
make changes to the actual image and you
can expand that and there are other
options available again I can then also
crop an image if I select an image and
select the crop tool you will see some
black bounding markers come around the
edge of the image so if I move those in
and then click away it will reduce the
size just don't do that by ctrl and said
so as you can see if I wanted to reduce
the size of that image so that one's
more square this one's more rectangular
so I click on the image select the crop
to move it in from the side so it's more
square click away that will
automatically do that and I can be size
it so it is more in keeping with the
image on the left hand side so the more
or less the same size now as well as
that you can actually group your items
together so if I want to make sure that
whatever are formatting I apply to that
image is also applied to that one I can
link them together so if I click on that
I image and then hold down the ctrl key
and click on that image I can now go to
the group objects icon and select group
so that there's no group just together
so as you see if I go now to the picture
Styles bar and start moving along the
icons and will change them to whichever
icon I select them it changes both
images so I'll select that on this or
both images are now linked so whatever
apply to one will automatically be
applied to the other again if you wish
to ungroup them you would just simply go
to which other highlighted other box
that is surrounding them is highlighted
go to go to ungroup and then that means
that they are now individual thank you
one other feature that like the
demonstration is how you can actually
place an image behind text so at the
moment I've inserted the images into the
presentation if I click on the image and
move it around it will automatically
cover the text so I just leave that
there
I'll do that with that one so at the
moment they are now covering the text
but if I right-click on the image they
can then send to back so they send it
backwards and again for that one sent
back it automatically allows the text to
be sure the images and a background it
may not look nice aesthetically but it
isn't something that you can do I could
increase the size of that and again the
size of that as you can see it would
still have the text so I could change
the highlight the text and change the
color to make it more emphasized and
again with the sales report so those are
various features and tools just to
enhance the document as you can see this
the style that has been applied to the
image is also giving it a shadow image